You learned to live in shifting sands With no
safe place to ever land You learned that doors
could slam and lock Against the ticking of the
clock You learn to touch could be a cage A quiet
simmering bit of rage But that old world is dead
and gone It's time to face a brand new dawn So let
my arms be your new one To catch you every time you
fall This heart of stands, it will not break For
your own precious, gentle sake If it's a heart
that you should need A simple, pure, loving
creed Then I am here, my love is true
My arms will be a home for you.
No need to brace, no need to hide With your two
sisters by your side We'll be the lock, we'll be
the key To your own safe reality We'll be the roof
against the rain To wash away the hurt and pain
This is a vow we'll always keep
While you are in your troubled sleep